WAHEED AISHAT ABIDEMI

Front-End Developer

KNOWLEDGE OF

Documentation

presentation

Graphic design

MS office

OBJECTIVE

An ambitious and focused youth . Aishat is a renounced frontend & wordpress developer, she has 2 years of experience in building, developing and managing websites, applications and programs for various companies.. She has her interest in pursuing projects that allows her to use her. acquired skills to achieve stated goals.

STRENGTHS

- Proficient in HTML5, CSS 3, Javascript.
- Excellent in using Front End frameworks—bootstrap
- understanding of responsive design principles
- Possess a knack for teamwork and comfortable working cross functional

PERSONAL SKILLS

Communicating

Organising

Prioritising

Decision making

Problem solving

Typing

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017– till date: ViviAfrica Chief Technology Officer (CTO) Responsibilities:

- Designs and develops website of company.
 - Monitoring and assessing new technologies.
- Managing multiple projects with other team mates.

2017– till date: TEXTYLE-KULTURE Chief Technology Officer (CTO) Responsibilities:

- Focusing on solving scientific and technological issues in the company.
- Creating and developing website unique websites for customers.
- Supporting the media and marketing department in the aspect of digital development.

EDUCATION

2013- present: LADOKE AKINTOLA UNIVERSITY OFTECHNOLOGY, OGBOMOSO, OYO STATE, NIGERIA;

B-Tech. pure & applied chemistry.

2018: UDACITY

Online certification course: Front End Development.

PERSONAL

DETAILS

(+234) 08140308878

Waheedaishat@gmail.com

Status: single

Obaafunbiowo estate,

okearo akure,

Ondo-state, Nigeria.

2007-2013: st peters unity secondary school, akure, ondostate.

St peter's unity sec school, akure.

West African senior school certificate examination (WASSCE).

TRAINING PROGRAMS:

pagecarton bootcamp, edx online :Web Development with HTML5 with CSS3, freecodecamp : Advanced Mobile & Responsive, Web Design Course & JavaScript.

HOBBIES & INTEREST

Waheed Aishat Abidemi is a creative fashion-Techie..Her passion for and solving problems has made her woven into technology aside being a chemist. She's a member of Aiesec Nigeria, and alumnus of common purpose global leadership experience. She likes to network, meet with great minds & also a volunteer for environmental charity.